Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures and Audiorecordings Documenting Football
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, motion pictures and audiorecordings documenting football
1916-2005
RU 971
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2648
(4115 items)
The materials consist of 16mm motion picture films, videotapes, and audiocassettes documenting football at Yale. Included are game films for the varsity, freshman, and junior varsity teams, footage of scrimmages, season highlights, a multi-part history of Yale football, and several Yale football-related productions.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2004-2007; gift of John Kieffer, 2013.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies (designated by a box with a 'U' suffix), or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession and thereunder chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of 16mm motion picture films, videotapes, and audiocassettes documenting football at Yale. Included are game films for the varsity, freshman, and junior varsity teams, footage of scrimmages, season highlights, a multi-part history of Yale football, and several Yale football-related productions.
College athletes; College sports; Football; Motion pictures (visual works); Videotapes; Yale University -- Football; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Football game films, 1916-1935; Accession 2006-A-028
  - Harvard, 1916; 1 (Box 1)
  - Princeton, 1923; 3 (Box 2–4)
    - Use copy for boxes 2-4, 1 (Box 2U)
  - Army, 1924; 1 (Box 6)
  - Brown, 1926; 1 (Box 5)
  - Army, 1926; 2 (Box 6–7)
  - Princeton, 1926; 2 (Box 8–9)
  - Harvard, 1926; 3 (Box 10–12)
  - Brown, 1927; 1 (Box 13)
  - Princeton, 1927; 2 (Box 14–15)
  - Harvard, 1927; 2 (Box 16–17)
  - Brown, 1928; 1 (Box 18)
  - Army, 1928 October; 1 (Box 19)
  - Army Highlights, 1928 October; 1 (Reel 109)
  - Princeton, 1928; 2 (Box 20–21)
  - Harvard, 1928; 3 (Box 22–24)
  - Army/Dartmouth/Princeton, 1928; 1 (Box 25)
  - Brown, 1929; 1 (Box 26)
  - Maryland, 1929; 1 (Box 27)
  - Princeton, 1929; 2 (Box 28, Box 101)
  - Army Highlights, 1929; 3 (Box 29–30, Box 100)
  - Harvard, 1929; 4 (Box 31–34)
  - Harvard, 1929; 1 (Box 103)
  - Dartmouth, 1929; 1 (Box 102)
  - Army/Dartmouth/Princeton/Harvard Highlights, 1929; 1 (Box 35)
  - Yale Games, 1929; 1 (Box 36)
  - Dartmouth, 1930; 3 (Box 37–39)
  - Army, 1930; 3 (Box 40–42)
  - Harvard, 1930; 2 (Box 43–44)
    - Duplicating Master, 1 (Box 43D)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 43U)
  - Army/Harvard Highlights, 1930; 1 (Box 45)
  - Princeton, 1930; 1 (Box 104)
  - Georgia, 1931; 2 (Box 47–48)
  - Army, 1931; 2 (Box 49–50)
  - Princeton, 1931; 2 (Box 51–52)
  - Harvard, 1931; 3 (Box 53–55)
  - Dartmouth, 1931; 1 (Box 56)
  - Harvard, 1932; 2 (Box 57–58)
  - Army, 1932; 2 (Box 59–60)
  - Princeton, 1932; 1 (Box 61)
  - Army, 1933; 2 (Box 62–63)
  - Brown, 1933; 2 (Box 64–65)
  - Dartmouth, 1933; 2 (Box 66–67)
  - Georgia, 1933; 1 (Box 68)
  - Harvard, 1933; 2 (Box 69–70)
  - Columbia, 1934; 2 (Box 71–72)
  - Brown, 1934; 2 (Box 73–74)
  - Army, 1934; 2 (Box 75–76)
  - Dartmouth, 1934; 2 (Box 77–78)
  - Georgia, 1934; 1 (Box 79)
  - Harvard, 1934; 3 (Box 80–82)
  - Princeton, 1934, 1935; 1 (Box 106)
  - Penn, 1934; 2 (Box 107–108)
  - New Hampshire, 1935; 2 (Box 83–84)
  - Penn, 1935; 1 (Box 85)
  - Navy, 1935; 2 (Box 86–87)
  - Army, 1935; 2 (Box 88–89)
  - Dartmouth, 1935; 2 (Box 90–91)
  - Brown, 1935; 2 (Box 92–93)
  - Princeton, 1935; 2 (Box 94–95)
  - Harvard, 1935; 2 (Box 96–97)
  - Princeton/Harvard Highlights, 1935; 1 (Box 98)
  - Harvard, 1935; 1 (Box 99)
  - Navy, 1935; 1 (Box 105)
- Football game videotapes, 1923-2005; Accession 2006-A-031
  Scope and Contents
  Several videotapes from this accession were removed and designated as use copies for films in other accessions.
  - Harvard, 1923; 1 (Box 1-D)
    - Use Copy, 1 (Box 1U)
  - Princeton, 1933; 1 (Box 2)
  - Princeton, undated; 1 (Box 13)
  - Princeton, 1950s; 1 (Box 19)
  - UConn, 1970; 1 (Box 40)
  - Harvard highlights (NESN), 1968; 1 (Box 20)
    General
    Commercially produced.
  - Cornell, 1970; 1 (Box 40)
  - Dartmouth (2nd half), 1970; 1 (Box 40)
  - Penn, 1970; 1 (Box 40)
  - Princeton Offensive Highlights, Harvard Offensive Highlights, 1976-77; 1 (Box 48)
    - Duplicating Masters, 7
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 48U)
  - Columbia Highlights, 1978; 1 (Box 54)
  - Cornell, 1979 November 3; 3 (Box 56–58)
  - UConn highlights, 1980-1981; 1 (Box 66)
  - Dartmouth, 1981 October 31; 3 (Box 67–69)
  - Penn, 1985 October 26; 3 (Box 82–84)
  - Cornell, 1985 November 10; 3 (Box 85–87)
  - Ivy League Football, 1986 October 25; 2 (Box 92–93)
  - Ivy League Football, 1986 November 22; 3 (Box 94–96)
  - New Hampshire, 1986-1987; 1 (Box 100)
  - Football at Yale, 1987 August 24; 4 (Box 103–106)
  - Columbia, 1987 October 17; 3 (Box 107–109)
  - Dartmouth, 1987 October 31; 3 (Box 110–112)
  - Cornell, 1987 November 7; 4 (Box 113–116)
  - Harvard, 1987 November 21; 3 (Box 117–119)
  - Penn State, 1987; 1 (Box 121)
  - UConn highlights, 1987; 1 (Box 122)
  - Brown, 1988 September 22; 4 (Box 125–128)
  - Cornell, 1988 November 8; 4 (Box 129–132)
  - Harvard, 1988 November 28; 4 (Box 133–136)
  - Army promo, 1 (Box 137)
  - Dartmouth, 1989 October 17; 4 (Box 141–144)
  - Penn offense, 1989; 1 (Box 146)
  - Highlights, 1989; 1 (Box 147)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 147U1)
  - UConn - Yale offense vs. UConn defense, 1990 September 29; 1 (Box 149)
  - Cornell - Yale defense vs. Cornell Offense, 1990; 1 (Box 641)
  - Princeton, 1990 November 10; 3 (Box 152–154)
    - Use copy for boxes 152-154, 1 (Box 152U)
  - Princeton - Yale offense vs. Princeton defense, 1990 November 10; 1 (Box 161)
  - Princeton - Yale defense vs. Princeton defense, 1990 November 10; 1 (Box 162)
  - Harvard, 1990 November 17; 5 (Box 155–159)
    - Use copy for boxes 155-159, 1 (Box 155U)
  - Harvard, side view, 1990 November 17; 1 (Box 160)
  - Highlights, 1990; 1 (Box 163)
  - UNH, 1991 September 7; 1 (Box 164)
  - Blue & White Scrimmage, 1991 September 12; 1 (Box 165)
  - Brown, 1991 September 21; 1 (Box 166)
  - Brown, end zone (tight shot continuous), 1991 September 21; 1 (Box 638)
  - Brown, end zone (continuous), 1991 September 21; 1 (Box 639)
  - Brown (Yale defense), 1991 September 21; 1 (Box 167)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 167U)
  - Brown (Yale offense), 1991 September 21; 1 (Box 168)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 168U)
  - Brown (Yale kicking), 1991 September 21; 1 (Box 169)
  - Holy Cross, 1991 September 26; 1 (Box 170)
  - Brown (frosh), 1991 September 27; 1 (Box 171)
  - Milford Academy, 1991 September 28; 1 (Box 172)
  - Lafayette, 1991 September 28; 1 (Box 173)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 173U)
  - Lafayette (Yale defense), 1991 September 28; 1 (Box 174)
  - Lafayette (Yale offense), 1991 September 28; 1 (Box 175)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 175U)
  - Lafayette (Yale kicking), 1991 September 28; 1 (Box 176)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 176U)
  - UConn (wide continuous sideview), 1991 October 5; 1 (Box 177)
  - UConn (tight endzone), 1991 October 5; 1 (Box 178)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 178U)
  - UConn (Yale offense -wide side), 1991 October 5; 1 (Box 179)
  - UConn (Yale offense -sideline, endzone), 1991 October 5; 1 (Box 180)
  - UConn (Yale defense), 1991 October 5; 1 (Box 181)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 181U)
  - UConn (Yale kicking), 1991 October 5; 1 (Box 182)
  - Colgate, 1991 October 6; 1 (Box 183)
  - UNH (JV), 1991 October 7; 1 (Box 184)
  - Colgate, 1991 October 12; 1 (Box 185)
  - Colgate (Yale defense), 1991 October 12; 1 (Box 186)
  - Colgate (Yale offense), 1991 October 12; 1 (Box 187)
  - Colgate (Yale kicking), 1991 October 12; 1 (Box 188)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 188U)
  - Dartmouth (frosh), 1991 October 18; 1 (Box 189)
  - Dartmouth (wide continuous side), 1991 October 19; 1 (Box 190)
  - Dartmouth (endzone), 1991 October 19; 1 (Box 191)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 191U)
  - Dartmouth (Yale defense), 1991 October 19; 1 (Box 192)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 192U)
  - Dartmouth (Yale offense), 1991 October 19; 1 (Box 193)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 193U)
  - Dartmouth (Yale kicking), 1991 October 19; 1 (Box 194)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 194U)
  - Columbia (wide side), 1991 October 25; 1 (Box 195)
  - Columbia (endzone), 1991 October 25; 1 (Box 196)
  - Columbia (endzone), 1991 October 26; 1 (Box 197)
  - Columbia (Yale defense), 1991 October 26; 1 (Box 198)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 198U)
  - Columbia (Yale offense), 1991 October 26; 1 (Box 199)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 199U)
  - Columbia (Yale kick), 1991 October 26; 1 (Box 200)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 200U)
  - Penn (side view), 1991 November 2; 1 (Box 201)
  - Penn (endzone), 1991 November 2; 1 (Box 202)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 202U)
  - Penn (Yale defense), 1991 November 2; 1 (Box 203)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 203U)
  - Penn (Yale offense), 1991 November 2; 1 (Box 204)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 204U)
  - Penn (Yale kicking), 1991 November 2; 1 (Box 205)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 205U)
  - Cornell, 1991 November 9; 2 (Box 206–207)
  - Cornell (wide shot), 1991 November 9; 1 (Box 208)
  - Cornell (tight shot), 1991 November 9; 1 (Box 209)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 209U)
  - Cornell (tight shot defense), 1991 November 9; 1 (Box 210)
  - Cornell (tight shot offense), 1991 November 9; 1 (Box 211)
  - Cornell (wide sideline defense), 1991 November 9; 1 (Box 212)
  - Cornell (wide sideline offense), 1991 November 9; 1 (Box 213)
    - Cornell (Yale kicking), 1991 November 9; 1 (Box 214)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 214U)
  - Princeton (wide sideline), 1991 November 16; 1 (Box 215)
  - Princeton (endzone), 1991 November 16; 1 (Box 216)
  - Princeton (Yale defense), 1991 November 16; 1 (Box 217)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 217U)
  - Princeton (Yale offense), 1991 November 16; 1 (Box 218)
  - Princeton (Yale kicking), 1991 November 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 219)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 219U)
  - Harvard (frosh), 1991 November 22; 1 (Box 220)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 220U)
  - Harvard, 1991 November 23; 4 (Box 221–223, Box 631)
  - Harvard (wide continuous sideview), 1991 November 23; 1 (Box 224)
  - Harvard (endzone), 1991 November 23; 1 (Box 225)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 225U1)
  - Harvard (Yale defense), 1991 November 23; 1 (Box 226)
  - Harvard (Yale kick), 1991 November 23; 1 (Box 227)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 227U)
  - Harvard (TV copy), 1991; 2 (Box 228–229)
  - Harvard (Red zone defense), 1991; 1 (Box 230)
  - Penn (frosh), 1991; 1 (Box 231)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 231U)
  - Princeton (frosh), 1991; 1 (Box 232)
  - Highlights, 1991; 1 (Box 233)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 233U1)
  - Union (JV), 1992 September 5; 2 (Box 234–235)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 235U)
  - Union (varsity), 1992 September 5; 2 (Box 236–237)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 236U)
  - Brown, 1992 September 19; 1 (Box 238)
  - Brown (frosh), 1992 September 24; 1 (Box 239)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 239U1)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 239U2)
  - Holy Cross (wide sideview), 1992; 1 (Box 240)
  - Holy Cross (tight endzone), 1992 September 26; 1 (Box 241)
  - Holy Cross, 1992; 1 (Box 242)
  - Milford Academy (JV), 1992 September 28; 1 (Box 243)
  - UConn (wide sideview), 1992 October 3; 1 (Box 244)
  - UConn (tight endzone), 1992 October 3; 1 (Box 245)
  - Fordham (wide sideline), 1992 October 10; 1 (Box 246)
  - Fordham (tight endzone), 1992 October 10; 1 (Box 247)
  - Fordham, 1992 October 10; 1 (Box 248)
  - Dartmouth (freshman), 1992 October 16; 1 (Box 249)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 249U)
  - Dartmouth (wide sideview), 1992 October 17; 1 (Box 250)
  - Dartmouth (endzone), 1992 October 17; 1 (Box 251)
  - Columbia (frosh), 1992 October 23; 1 (Box 252)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 252U)
  - Columbia (wide sideview), 1992 October 24; 1 (Box 253)
  - Columbia (tight shot), 1992 October 24; 1 (Box 254)
  - Columbia, 1992 October 24; 1 (Box 255)
  - Penn (wide sideview), 1992 October 31; 1 (Box 256)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 256U)
  - Penn (tight endzone), 1992 October 31; 1 (Box 257)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 257U)
  - Cornell (wide sideview), 1992 November 8; 1 (Box 258)
  - Cornell (tight shot), 1992 November 8; 1 (Box 259)
  - Princeton (tight shot), 1992 November 14; 1 (Box 260)
  - Princeton, 1992 November 14; 1 (Box 261)
  - Harvard (frosh), 1992 November 20; 1 (Box 262)
    - Use copy 1, 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 262U1)
    - Use copy 2, 1 (Box 262U2)
  - Harvard, 1992 November 21; 3 (Box 263–265)
  - Penn (frosh), 1992; 1 (Box 266)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 266U)
  - Highlights, 1992; 1 (Box 267)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 267U)
  - Football, narration (Gonillo), 1992; 1 (Box 647)
  - Union (sideview), 1993 September 4; 1 (Box 268)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 268U)
  - Union (endzone), 1993 September 4; 1 (Box 269)
  - Blue White Scrimmage, 1993 September 9; 1 (Box 270)
  - Brown (wide sideline), 1993 September 18; 1 (Box 271)
  - Brown (Yale offense), 1993 September 18; 1 (Box 272)
  - Brown (Yale defense), 1993 September 18; 1 (Box 273)
  - Brown (Yale kick), 1993 September 18; 1 (Box 274)
  - Brown (tight endzone), 1993 September 18; 2 (Box 275–276)
  - Brown, 1993 September 18; 2 (Box 277–278)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 277U)
  - UConn, 1993; 1 (Box 278)
  - Brown (JV), 1993 September 20; 2 (Box 279–280)
  - UConn (tight endzone), 1993 September 25; 1 (Box 281)
  - UConn (Yale offense), 1993 September 25; 1 (Box 282)
  - UConn (Yale defense), 1993 September 25; 1 (Box 283)
  - UConn (Yale kicking), 1993 September 25; 1 (Box 284)
  - Harvard (JV), 1993 September 27; 1 (Box 285)
  - UConn (Yale defense), 1993 October 1; 1 (Box 286)
  - University of Central Florida (wide sideline), 1993 October 2; 1 (Box 287)
  - University of Central Florida (endzone), 1993 October 2; 1 (Box 288)
  - University of Central Florida, 1993 October 2; 1 (Box 289)
  - University of Central Florida (Yale offense), 1993 October 2; 1 (Box 290)
  - University of Central Florida (Yale defense), 1993 October 2; 1 (Box 291)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 291U)
  - University of Central Florida (Yale kicking), 1993 October 2; 1 (Box 292)
  - Holy Cross (wide sideline), 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 293)
  - Holy Cross (tight endzone), 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 294)
  - Holy Cross (Yale offense), 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 295)
  - Holy Cross (Yale defense), 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 296)
  - Holy Cross (Yale kicking), 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 297)
  - Holy Cross (TV film), 1993 October 9; 1 (Box 298)
  - Holy Cross (Sports channel), 1993 October 9; 2 (Box 299–300)
    Commercially-produced.
  - Holy Cross, 1993 October 9; 3 (Box 301–303)
  - Dartmouth (JV), 1993 October 15; 1 (Box 304)
  - Dartmouth, 1993 October 16; 1 (Box 305)
  - Dartmouth (tight endzone), 1993 October 16; 2 (Box 306–307)
  - Dartmouth (Yale offense), 1993 October 16; 1 (Box 308)
  - Dartmouth (Yale defense), 1993 October 16; 1 (Box 309)
  - Dartmouth (Yale kicking), 1993 October 16; 1 (Box 310)
  - Dartmouth, 1993; 2 (Box 311–312)
  - Columbia (JV), 1993 October 22; 1 (Box 313)
  - Columbia (wide sideline), 1993 October 23; 1 (Box 314)
  - Columbia (tight endzone), 1993 October 23; 1 (Box 315)
  - Columbia (Yale offense), 1993 October 23; 1 (Box 316)
  - Columbia (Yale defense), 1993 October 23; 1 (Box 317)
  - Columbia (Yale kicking), 1993 October 23; 1 (Box 318)
  - Milford Academy (JV), 1993 October 29; 1 (Box 319)
  - Penn (wide sideline), 1993 October 30; 1 (Box 320)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 320U)
  - Penn (tight endzone), 1993 (Box 321)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 321U)
  - Penn (Yale offense), 1993 October 30; 1 (Box 322)
  - Penn (Yale defense), 1993 October 30; 1 (Box 323)
  - Penn (Yale kick), 1993 October 30; 1 (Box 324)
  - Cornell (wide continuous sideview), 1993 November 6; 1 (Box 325)
  - Cornell (Yale offense), 1993 November 6; 1 (Box 326)
  - Cornell (Yale defense), 1993 November 6; 1 (Box 327)
  - Cornell (Yale kick), 1993 November 6; 1 (Box 328)
  - Princeton (wide sideline), 1993 November 13; 1 (Box 329)
  - Princeton (tight endzone), 1993 November 13; 1 (Box 330)
  - Princeton (Yale offense), 1993 November 13; 1 (Box 331)
  - Princeton (Yale defense), 1993 November 13; 1 (Box 332)
  - Princeton (Yale kick), 1993 November 13; 1 (Box 333)
  - Princeton, 1993 November 13; 4 (Box 334–337)
  - Havard (JV), 1993 November 20; 1 (Box 338)
  - Harvard (wide sideline), 1993 November 20; 2 (Box 339–340)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 339U–340U)
  - Harvard (tight endzone), 1993 November 20; 1 (Box 341)
  - Harvard (Yale offense), 1993 November 20; 1 (Box 342)
  - Harvard (Yale defense), 1993 November 20; 1 (Box 343)
  - Harvard (Yale kick), 1993 November 20; 1 (Box 344)
  - Harvard (TV), 1993 November 20; 2 (Box 345–346)
    - Use copy for box 345 (first half), 1 (Box 345U)
  - Harvard, 1993 November 20; 3 (Box 347–349)
  - Harvard (VinCam), 1993; 2 (Box 350–351)
  - Highlights, 1993; 1 (Box 352)
  - Plymouth St., 1994 September 3; 2 (Box 353–354)
  - Plymouth St. (Yale kicking), 1994September 3; 1 (Box 355)
  - Blue White (sideline), 1994 September 8; 1 (Box 356)
  - Blue White (endzone), 1994 September 8; 1 (Box 357)
  - Coast Guard Academy (JV), 1994 September 9; 1 (Box 358)
  - Brown (sideline wide continuous), 1994 September 17; 1 (Box 359)
  - Brown (endzone tight), 1994 September 17; 1 (Box 360)
  - Brown (Yale offense), 1994 September 17; 1 (Box 361)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 361U)
  - Brown (Yale defense), 1994 September 17; 1 (Box 362)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 362U)
  - Brown (Yale kicking), 1994 September 17; 1 (Box 363)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 363U)
  - Brown (JV -wide sideline), 1994 September 19; 1 (Box 364)
  - Brown (JV -tight), 1994 September 19; 1 (Box 365)
  - Brown (JV -endzone), 1994 September 19; 1 (Box 366)
  - Holy Cross (wide continuous side), 1994 September 24; 1 (Box 367)
  - Holy Cross (endzone), 1994 September 24; 1 (Box 368)
  - Holy Cross (Yale offense), 1994 September 24; 1 (Box 369)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 369U)
  - Holy Cross (Yale defense), 1994 September 24; 1 (Box 370)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 370U)
  - Holy Cross (Yale kicking), 1994 September 24; 1 (Box 371)
  - Freshmen vs. UConn? (wide continuous side), 1994 September 25; 1 (Box 372)
  - UConn (wide continuous side), 1994 October 1; 1 (Box 373)
  - UConn (tight endzone), 1994 October 1; 1 (Box 374)
  - UConn (Yale offense), 1994 October 1; 1 (Box 375)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 375U)
  - UConn (Yale defense), 1994 October 1; 1 (Box 376)
  - UConn (Yale kick), 1994 October 1; 1 (Box 377)
  - Lehigh (wide continuous sideline), 1994 October 8; 1 (Box 378)
  - Lehigh (endzone), 1994 October 8; 1 (Box 379)
  - Lehigh (Yale offense), 1994 October 8; 1 (Box 380)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 380U)
  - Lehigh (Yale defense), 1994 October 8; 1 (Box 381)
  - Lehigh (Yale kick), 1994 October 8; 1 (Box 382)
  - Lehigh (TV), 1994 October 8; 2 (Box 383–384)
  - Dartmouth (wide), 1994; 1 (Box 385)
  - Dartmouth (tight), 1994; 1 (Box 386)
  - Dartmouth (endzone), 1994 October 15; 1 (Box 387)
  - Dartmouth (Yale offense), 1994 October 15; 1 (Box 388)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 388U)
  - Dartmouth (Yale defense), 1994 October 15; 1 (Box 389)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 389U)
  - Dartmouth (Yale kick), 1994 October 15; 1 (Box 390)
  - Columbia, 1994 October 22; 1 (Box 391)
  - Columbia (tight endzone), 1994 October 22; 1 (Box 392)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 392U1)
  - Columbia (Yale offense), 1994 October 22; 1 (Box 393)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 393U1)
      - Duplicate [missing], videotape (VHS) (Box 393U2)
  - Columbia (Yale defense), 1994 October 22; 1 (Box 394)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 394U)
  - Columbia (Yale kick), 1994 October 22; 1 (Box 395)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 395U)
  - Columbia (JV), 1994 October 23; 1 (Box 396)
  - Penn, 1994 October 29; 1 (Box 397)
  - Penn (wide continuous sideline), 1994 October 29; 1 (Box 398)
  - Penn (endzone), 1994 October 29; 1 (Box 399)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 399U)
  - Penn (Yale offense), 1994 October 29; 1 (Box 400)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 400U1)
  - Penn (Yale defense), 1994 October 29; 1 (Box 401)
  - Penn (Yale kick), 1994 October 29; 1 (Box 402)
  - Penn (TV copy), 1994 October 29; 2 (Box 403–404)
  - Milford Academy (JV), 1994 October 31; 1 (Box 405)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 405U)
  - Cornell, 1994 November 5; 1 (Box 406)
  - Cornell (endzone), 1994 November 5; 1 (Box 407)
  - Cornell (Yale offense), 1994 November 5; 1 (Box 408)
  - Cornell (Yale defense), 1994 November 5; 1 (Box 409)
  - Cornell (Yale kick), 1994 November 5; 1 (Box 410)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 410U)
  - Cornell (TV), 1994 November 5; 2 (Box 411–412)
  - Princeton, 1994 November 12; 1 (Box 413)
  - Princeton (endzone), 1994 November 12; 1 (Box 414)
  - Princeton (Yale offense), 1994 November 12; 1 (Box 415)
  - Princeton (Yale defense), 1994 November 12; 1 (Box 416)
  - Princeton (Yale kick), 1994 November 12; 1 (Box 417)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 417U)
  - Blue White, 1994 November 13; 1 (Box 418)
  - Harvard (wide continuous sideline), 1994 November 19; 1 (Box 419)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 419U1)
  - Harvard (endzone), 1994 November 19; 1 (Box 420)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 420U)
  - Harvard, 1994 November 19; 1 (Box 421)
  - Harvard (Yale offense), 1994 November 19; 1 (Box 422)
  - Harvard (Yale defense), 1994 November 19; 1 (Box 423)
  - Harvard (Yale kicking), 1994 November 19; 1 (Box 424)
  - Harvard (ESPN2), 1994 November 19; 2 (Box 425–426)
    - Use copy (part 1), 1 (Box 425U1)
    - Use copy (part 2), 1 (Box 426U1)
  - Yale Football, 1994; 5 (Box 427–431)
  - Dartmouth (JV), 1994; 1 (Box 432)
  - Harvard (JV), 1994; 1 (Box 433)
  - Highlights, 1994; 1 (Box 434)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 434U1)
  - Highlights, 1994; 1 (Box 436)
  - Cozza's 30 Years at Yale, 1 (Box 436)
  - Plymouth State (Yale defense), 1995 September 2; 1 (Box 435)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 435U)
  - Brown (sideline wide), 1995 September 16; 1 (Box 436)
  - Brown (endzone), 1995 September 16; 1 (Box 437)
  - Brown (Yale defense), 1995 September 16; 1 (Box 438)
  - Brown (Yale kicking), 1995 September 16; 1 (Box 439)
  - Lehigh (wide sideline), 1995 September 23; 1 (Box 440)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 440U)
  - Lehigh (endzone), 1995 September 23; 1 (Box 441)
  - Lehigh (Yale offense), 1995 September 23; 1 (Box 442)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 442U1)
  - Lehigh (Yale offense, sideline wide), 1995 September 23; 1 (Box 645)
  - Lehigh (Yale defense), 1995 September 23; 1 (Box 443)
  - UConn (wide sideline), 1995 September 30; 1 (Box 444)
  - UConn (endzone), 1995 September 30; 1 (Box 445)
  - UConn (Yale offense), 1995 September 30; 1 (Box 446)
  - UConn (Yale defense), 1995 September 30; 1 (Box 447)
  - UConn (Yale kicking), 1995 September 30; 1 (Box 448)
  - Holy Cross (wide sideline), 1995 October 7; 1 (Box 449)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 449U1)
  - Holy Cross (endzone), 1995 October 7; 1 (Box 450)
  - Holy Cross (Yale offense), 1995 October 7; 1 (Box 451)
  - Holy Cross (Yale defense), 1995 October 7; 1 (Box 452)
  - Holy Cross (Yale kicking), 1995 October 7; 1 (Box 453)
  - Holy Cross (TV 3), 1995 October 7; 2 (Box 454–455)
  - Dartmouth (JV), 1995 October 13; 1 (Box 456)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 456U1)
  - Dartmouth, 1995; 1 (Box 457)
  - Dartmouth (endzone), 1995 October 14; 1 (Box 458)
  - Dartmouth (Yale offense), 1995 October 14; 1 (Box 459)
  - Dartmouth (Yale defense), 1995 October 14; 1 (Box 460)
  - Dartmouth (Yale kicking), 1995 October 14; 1 (Box 461)
  - Columbia (wide sideline), 1995 October 21; 1 (Box 462)